best-deal.com 2012-05-26

# Privacy | Price comparison and reviews at best-deal.com

The security of your personal information and your privacy is very important to us as operator of BEST-DEAL.com (in the following just called BEST-DEAL.com). Since your trust in us means a lot to us, we'll do all that's possible to warrant and keep this trust. Against this background BEST-DEAL.com tries by all means to ensure the compliance of privacy. In this regard we ask you to read the privacy policy to get informed about the way we'll treat your personal information if you use our online services. Changes in this policy might happen from time to time and will be posted on the BEST-DEAL.com website.

#### a) Your Privacy

BEST-DEAL.com is brought to you by the Unister GmbH ("PREISVERGLEICH.de"). BEST-DEAL.com believes that trust is an important component of the service we provide to our customers. To ensure that we earn and keep that trust, BEST-DEAL.com makes every effort to protect your privacy and the confidentiality of your personal information. This Privacy Policy is provided to inform you about BEST-DEAL.com's collection, use and disclosure of information you choose to share with us through our website.

This Privacy Policy is considered to be a part of BEST-DEAL.com's User Agreement. By using the site you agree to the terms and conditions of the User Agreement, including this Privacy Policy. By using the site, you are also consenting to BEST-DEAL.com's privacy practices, including the use and disclosure of any personally identifiable information that you have shared with us, as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### b) Minor's Privacy

BEST-DEAL.com is not targeted towards, or intended for use by anyone under the age of 18. By using the website you represent and warrant that you are 18 years of age or older.

#### c) Use Of Cookies On Our Website

BEST-DEAL.com uses "cookies" to automatically recognize returning users. A cookie is a small file on your hard drive that allows us to display your previously defined search criteria and notification preferences whenever you visit our site. The information saved is used for the functionality of the site, for example, by recording your display preferences or regulating the frequency of pop-ups. Advertising partners also use cookies over which BEST-DEAL.com has no control. These are used to select customer-specific advertising.

You are free to block cookies from being saved on your hard disk by configuring your browser appropriately. It is not necessary to enable cookies to be able to use our website. However, we draw your attention to the fact that blocking cookies can lead to restricted function.

#### d) Other Data Collection

We may get data from or about you in other ways not specifically described in this statement. For example, you might contact customer support or we may get a third party complaint about you.

#### e) Use Of Information

Information you provide to us through the website is used by BEST-DEAL.com to operate the website, provide you with information and services you request, and to communicate with you. We may, for example, use information you provide to target ads that we think you may be interested in, or send emails to you including newsletters and alerts. Your information may also be used to contact you when necessary (such as to assist you in your use of the website). You may always choose not to provide us with this information. However, this may limit our ability to provide you with a specific service. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time.

#### f) Transfer Of Personal Data

Your personal data will be passed on to our customers in anonymous form only. BEST-DEAL.com does not publish any of your personal information without your express consent or unless we are legally obliged to do so.

#### g) Protection From Web Crawlers And Spam

BEST-DEAL.com guarantees that we will only use your e-mail address with your express permission for the uses described in the conditions of use. We will not sell your e-mail address to third parties and will prevent your e-mail address from being captured by web crawlers and spiders to the extent that is it within our capability to do so. If you think that your e-mail address has been captured in this way, please contact our technical support team immediately.

#### h) Changes To These Privacy Guidelines

Any changes to the privacy guidelines will be posted on the BEST-DEAL.com website.
